

PERSONAL DETAILS

Name	Jeff Ginsburg
Web	http://www.jginsburg.com
Contact	919.601.9888
Email	√ jeginsburg@gmail.com

EDUCATION

Drexel University (Philadelphia, PA) College Bachelor of Science in Digital Media Graduated Cum Laude



EXPERIENCE

Sizmek

October 2013 - Present

Creative Mobile Developer, Team Lead - East Coast

- Build rich media for mobile web, desktop and in-app utilizing HTML5, CSS, and Javascript under tight deadlines.
- Act as a liaison between editorial and development teams
- Collaborate with Project Managers, Traffic Managers, and Art Directors to gather campaign info to help build and scope projects
- Translate client files (HTML/PSD's/PDF's) to work with Pointroll's proprietary platform
- Ensure campaigns function properly on publisher pages across all devices and browsers
- Manage a team of 4 developers dealing with all non-automotive work

Miles Technologies

June 2010 - June 2013

Senior Graphical & User Interface Developer

- Responsible for creation of web interfaces, master pages and control skinning for custom software solutions.
- Responsible for quality of user interfaces designed for all custom developed software applications as well as new and existing feature development.
- Responsible for coordinating mockups for all new system designs.
- Coordinate graphics integration to applications.
- Analyze UI for systems during QA phase of project in order to provide recommendations on modifying the code / display in order to be more user-friendly and/or intuitive.

Purple Lion Design

Sept. 2011 - Present

Co-Founder, Web Developer, Project Manager

- Responsible for creation of all graphics and user interface related items.
- Responsibilities Include initial project designs, master page creation, UI updates as well as marketing & branding decisions.
- Work for custom software clients include designing, mocking up and developing screens for corporate websites, Greek Solutions products and all additional custom software solutions.



PROFILE



- f facebook.com/jeff.ginsburg.39
- in linkedin.com/in/jeffginsburg

I am a hybrid User Interface Developer and a Front-End Developer that focuses on websites that are both stylish and intuitive. Throughout my career I have created applications and responsive websites for desktop, tablet, and mobile devices; and I have had the pleasure of creating work for companies ranging from luxury automotive manufacturers to small family-owned businesses. Complete descriptions of companies I have worked with can be found below, in my resume and in the UI Design, Web Development and Mobile Ad

I enjoy creating designs that not only catch the eye for being visually attractive, but also surprise with their simplicity and ease of use. I see the web as an ever changing entity, and I use new technology that produces better results.



SKILLS



Specialties

Web Design User Interface Design Mobile Ad Creation Logo Design



Knowledge

Design Typography **Technical Writing** Responsive Design **Project Management** Typography



Languages/Software/SDK

Adobe Creative Suite HTML/HTML5 CSS/CSS3 Javascript **j**Query **MRAID** AdMob AdMarvel

MoPub Wordpress Blogger

Microsoft Office